Mai... No,
Aiko.
I'm embarrassed.
You can be yourself.
Show it to me, and only me,
your true self.
A dream?!
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 5]
I'm glad it was a dream.
And? What about you?
What about me?
In other words, do you want to do it with Reo?
- What?
- Have sex.
N-No, well...
How to put it...?
Maybe your desire became your dreams?
No, no, no way! What?!
Are you flustered?
I-I-I don't know!
It's my first time, so I don't get the timing and all that.
What about you?
In my case, I'd want to get intimate with the person I like.
As expected.
As for Reo and I...
Aren't you two going to an amusement park?
Maybe he'll ask about it on the way home.
- You think?
- Yup.
So that's how it goes.
You're not going on a date with that bra, are you?
Something wrong?
Sex appeal is key. That bra will do nothing for him.
Seriously? I don't own a proper bra.
Hold on, didn't you buy one in middle school?
It should be around here somewhere.
To think it'll be your time to shine.
[Listen, I want you to come as "Aiko" tomorrow.]
[It's a long way out, so we should be all right.]
Man, she's late.
What, you hitting on pigeons?
Ritsuki, you reek of alcohol.
I hit it off with this businessman.
We had a heated discussion about the future of Japan's economy,
and now look at the time.
I hear you have a date with Aiko?
Yes, though I've just been waiting.
Maybe she's prettying up.
Listen, I was worried about you two.
So as her elder brother, I made sure to give her
the "talk".
I leave her to you.
Bye bye!
What's his problem?
[Lodging for love, at half the price]
Reo!
Hey.
Why are you "Mai"?
See, I get a bit embarrassed as "Aiko".
Sorry.
You get a pass, cause you look cute today.
Come on, let's go.
There's so much to do.
It's amazing! Feels like a real date.
Since you're off today, when's your curfew?
Oh... uh... whenever.
I see.
Then we can take our time.
Is this about "that"?
You see... um...
Do you want to do it?
In other words... do "that" with me...
I don't know who told you what,
but don't be so stiff.
Of course I do.
But I plan to wait until you feel the same way.
Reo...
Let's just enjoy today without all that.
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
It's coming, it's coming!
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna go and take it ♫
Reo, can I spin faster?
How fun!
What should we ride next?
I want to ride the ferris wheel.
Let's ride that last.
Are you already tired?
Not at all. It's just, spinning rides aren't my forte.
Really? My bad.
I felt no sincerity.
You know, dates are super-duper fun!
That smile just now was unfair.
Found you!
The Morikawas...
Why are they here?
Getting a head start is unfair.
We're on a date.
Then I just came here to play with Takumi.
Yeah, apparently Ritsuki accidentally told Ikumi.
I tried texting you, but it seems you never saw it.
Seriously?
We met one another in such an open area. This must be fate!
- Sorry, could you stop that?
- Why?
Right, Reo?
He's right.
We're intruding on them.
I see. I'm terribly sorry.
I've never come with friends before,
so I got elated.
I'm sure it would be fun, if I went around with friends.
Is your answer a definite "No"?
Isn't that enough?
I really think that's enough.
I'm having fun!
I ended up yielding.
I like that good-natured part of you.
You don't have to like me.
Take her home, please.
It's been so long since I've seen Ikumi that happy.
Did you come along for her sake?
Oh yeah, go on ahead, Reo.
I don't understand the appeal of spinning.
Here, it's on me. Let's take a break.
You like this coffee, right?
Really?
Isn't it obvious I know what my crush prefers?
You didn't?
Plus, he likes collecting basketball t-shirts,
and his favorite sneaker brand—
My bad, I'm abstaining from coffee.
What? Why?
Mai doesn't like coffee,
so I thought she'd dislike our kisses.
Is that all?
Today, I'm on a date with Mai.
Don't meddle anymore.
Wait, Reo!
Didn't I ask you to seduce Mai?
Do you seriously like him?
I do.
Don't you just want to steal him away?
Takumi, you'll always be my ally, right?
I will.
If it's for you, I'd do anything.
Couldn't you have been kinder?
Be kind, and then what?
Was it... all for me?
I didn't want you to make that face.
How lame. I'm losing my cool.
Same here.
I didn't even know what you like.
Ikumi knew you better.
I felt frustrated.
I want to become someone
who understands you the most.
Just remain as you are, Aiko.
Even so, Ikumi looked so sad.
I don't want you to hurt her like that.
You're right.
I may have been a bit harsh.
- Let's head back.
- Yeah.
- Have you seen Ikumi?
- No, we haven't.
- I took my eyes off her, and she disappeared.
- What?
Pardon me.
- Reo! Did you find her?
- No.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
- I'll look over there.
- Then I'll go this way.
We've been looking for you. What're you doing? You haven't even answered your phone.
Mai!
- Sorry about all this.
- Why?
Because...
Don't worry, we'll find her.
Oh, found them! All right, let's go.
Wait up!
It's been my dream to ride a ferris wheel with my crush.
Same here.
- Then our dreams came true!
- Not mine.
After all, Mai's not here.
You're too cold to other girls, aside from Mai.
I have no interest in anyone but her.
Even so, I...
Why did we get on?
We should have waited on the ground.
Oh, you're right.
You must be an idiot.
Either way, I'm glad we found her.
Why do you look so happy?
Because Ikumi was safe and sound!
You're seriously good-natured.
Ikumi is trying to steal your boyfriend.
"Steal"?
I'm fine with receiving half of whatever Mai gets.
Just please, fall in love with me.
Ikumi has never failed in seducing a man.
What?
She's stolen boyfriends from ever single girl who's bullied her.
You have no chance of winning against her.
Plus, you're alone with me.
I'll protect Ikumi, no matter the method.
I'll do anything.
Anything...?
If necessary, I can sleep with some girl I don't care about.
Why?
Isn't it hard to lay hands on a girl who's had sex?
- What the hell?
- That's how I've protected her.
Is that what you want?
That's pretty sad.
- Like you'd understand—
- Yeah, I don't.
I don't understand at all.
But you know,
sleeping with some girl you don't love,
that's just sad!
You should worry about what's going on over there.
Aren't you worried?
"Worried"...
Morikawa,
I'm sure you'd become my ideal girlfriend.
You'd do your best to make me happy.
Of course I would.
Mai doesn't get that at all.
I have to put in all the effort.
It's a lot of work.
- In that case—
- Right now,
my love for Mai, feels greater than hers.
But she's doing her best to reciprocate.
That's why...
I want to treasure her.
I appreciate your confession,
but I'm sorry.
Ikumi!
Mai?
We were riding behind you guys.
Does that bother you?
- Wait!
- What do you want, let go!
Everyone was worried!
- At the very least, thank Takumi.
- Huh?
Don't you have more pressing complaints?
- Like what?
- You were fine with all that?
I was with Reo.
Why not get a little jealous?
I won't lose to you.
If you're serious, then I accept your challenge.
I won't lose either.
So stop stealing boys you have no interest in!
I see Takumi told you.
He's worried about you!
- He treats you preciously—
- I know!
I don't understand...
I don't understand why Reo likes you.
- Give it a rest!
- I hate people like you!
What the hell?
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
Let's go home.
Sorry to bother you two.
♫ So I won't let you go easy on me ♫
♫ I don't wish for anyone to know my secret ♫
Are you mad?
Not really.
Rather,
you were watching us, right?
Weren't you worried?
Well, I was, but…
"But"?
I...
trust in you.
Thanks, Aiko.
♫ I make you acting like a kid with just a sweet kiss ♫
♫ Only I know this ♫
♫ Rather than touching, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
To be honest, I was jealous.
I...
got jealous after hearing you rode the ferris wheel with Takumi.
♫ I'll steal you away before anyone gets the chance ♫
You got jealous?
Yeah, cause...
I want all of your "firsts".
Does that bother you?
Reo, you have it just as hard.
Mai's a busybody... no, she's too good-natured.
And I love her for all that.
How sweet.
You know, I understand how you feel.
Sounds like you're saying you like her too.
Yes, maybe that's it.
I... might like her.
[Next time]
Don't be alone with Takumi.
Those two suit one another.
You're free to fall in love with whoever you want.
I decided to be honest with myself.
- She's my toy.
- Why not find a new one?
- Were you testing me?
- That's what I want to say. Why did you lie?
You must have been so scared. Your legs gave out.